uadreams.com 2014-02-21

# Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

When you shop in our store, we will ask for your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses and telephone numbers. We also ask for your chosen method of payment (credit card or online payment service). Your payment information is securely transferred to a third party vendor for processing. We do not retain credit card or other payment identification information on our servers. In addition, we also log information about your visit to the store, including the URL that you came from, your Internet Protocol address, domain type (co.uk, com), Find pages that you view and search terms you use.

## How do we use personal information?

The information you provide to purchase 0 from us is used to fulfill your order. In addition, we use log information from us in order to enhance the operation of the Store. We do not correlate personally identifying information collected in database with any other information that you provide when using other of our products or services.

## What about cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. When you visit site, we set a cookie on your computer to help identify you, customize your experience and maintain your account and order information. To protect the security of your account, you must accept the site cookie in order to shop here.

## Do we share personal information?

We do not sell or rent any personal information to others. We may, however, disclose personal information if we believe we are required to do so by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of site, its users and the public. Personal information collected by site may be stored and processed in USA or any other country in which we or our agents maintain facilities. By using site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

## How do we keep your information secure?

The personal information that you provide to us, including your credit card or other payment information, is maintained on secure servers and protected by industry-standard Secure Socket Layer encryption. When entering personal information, look for an icon at the bottom of your browser window that indicates you are on a secure page.

## How do I update my information?

You can access and edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the “My account” links prior to confirming your order.

If you have questions about the status of your orders or any other questions about us, please contact us at support.
